<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>oecd clone</title>
  <link>http://www.oecd-CLONE.org</link>
<description>www.oecd.org</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<copyright>Copyright: (C).OECD</copyright>
  <docs>http://www.oecd.org/rss</docs>
		      <managingEditor>webmaster@oecd.org</managingEditor>
		      <webMaster>webmaster@oecd.org</webMaster>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Economy: Brazil reforms to spur competitiveness, productivity and trade would strengthen COVID-19 recovery]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 outbreak has brought Brazil’s economy back into recession, with swift government support helping millions of vulnerable households. A strong and inclusive recovery from the crisis that benefits all Brazilians will require additional ambitious reforms, the latest OECD Economic Survey of Brazil says.
]]></description>
  <link>http://www.oecd.org/newsroom/brazil-reforms-to-spur-competitiveness-productivity-and-trade-would-strengthen-covid-19-recovery.htm</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.oecd.org</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>        <item>
<title><![CDATA[Opinion: A multilateral agenda for a strong, resilient, green and inclusive recovery from COVID-19]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Only through collective action will we be able to 'build back better' towards more resilient, more inclusive and greener economies and societies. A strong ambition as we celebrate the OECD’s 60th anniversary: By President of the Spanish Government Pedro Sánchez and OECD Secretary-General Angel Gurría
]]></description>
  <link>http://www.oecd.org</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.oecd.org</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>        <item>
<title><![CDATA[Climate change: The Paris Agreement five years on–Taking stock and looking forward]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Saturday 12 December marks the 5th anniversary of the Paris Agreement, a comprehensive global plan to tackle climate change. In a special statement, OECD Secretary-General Angel Gurría points to the real opportunities in 2021 for driving progress on climate action and towards a sustainable recovery from the COVID-19 crisis.]]></description>
  <link>http://www.oecd.org</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.oecd.org</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 04:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>        <item>
<title><![CDATA[Tax evasion: International community reaches important milestone in fight against tax evasion]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[New international standards on the automatic exchange of financial account information for tax purposes have been deemed as satisfactorily implemented by countries worldwide. Some 88% of jurisdictions engaged in the exchange process have satisfactory legal frameworks in place, a milestone in the fight against tax evasion, a new report says.]]></description>
  <link>http://www.oecd.org/tax/international-community-reaches-important-milestone-in-fight-against-tax-evasion.htm</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.oecd.org</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>        <item>
<title><![CDATA[Health: Asia-Pacific countries have managed COVID-19 crisis relatively well but major challenges remain]]></title>
<description><![CDATA[Australia, Japan, Korea and New Zealand have done relatively well in addressing the COVID-19 epidemic and limiting the first wave of the virus, according to Health at a Glance Asia/Pacific 2020. The report is the OECD’s first analysis of the pandemic's impact on health systems and the policy responses in the Asia-Pacific region. 
]]></description>
  <link>http://www.oecd.org</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.oecd.org</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>        
</channel>
</rss>
